trickmillion.com 2017-11-19

# TrickMillion Privacy Policy

At **[Trick M](http://www.techgola.com/)illion**, the privacy of its visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information that is received and collected and how it is used.

###  Log Files

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

* Internet Protocol addresses (IP)

* Types of browser

* Internet Service Provider (ISP)

* Date and time stamp

* Referring and exit pages

* Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

###  Cookies

www.trickmillion..com does not use cookies.

www.trickmillion..com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

###  Google Analytics

www.trickmillion..com uses Google Analytics to collect information about the use of this site, such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit, and what other sites they came from. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the anonymised IP and plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.

###  Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

###  Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

###  Privacy Contact Information

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing email address to receive Latest Updates from TechGola. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog.

Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

If you have any Questions, Concerns, or Comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

E-mail: **[webmaster @trickmillion.com](mailto:webmaster@techgola.com)** – Contact Us

Last Updated: November 29, 2012

###  More information

If you require any more information or have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by using the contact form.

This Privacy Policy is subject to change and to being updated without notice.
